http://www.netshiftmedia.com/privacy-policy

Skip to Navigation
Skip to Content
Skip to Footer
1.250.314.0898    sales@netshiftmedia.com
HomeAboutMissionPhilosophyTechnologyServicesInternet MarketingWeb Site DesignWeb Application DevelopmentPortfolioWeb SitesClientsTestimonialsContactCareersDirections
Privacy Policy
As an Internet company, we understand the potential dangers in providing personal information over the Internet. With that in mind, we will make you well aware of any data that we collect from you through our web site. This privacy policy applies to all domains registered to Net Shift Media Inc. (“Net Shift Media”), and all company employees, contractors, and associates are bound to these terms.
Terms of Use
As well as this privacy policy, please review our “Terms of Use” to understand the terms that you agree to in accessing our web site before accessing the rest of our site.
External Links
Net Shift Media may link to third-party web sites for your reference. Net Shift Media does not control these domains, and cannot attest to the privacy policies of such sites. Any data provided to these sites is not covered by this policy and we suggest you review the privacy policies of such web sites before providing them with any personal information. This privacy policy only covers domains and Internet properties owned by, and under complete control of Net Shift Media.
Consent
By accessing this site, you are agreeing to the data collection outlined in this document. To keep you informed as this policy changes, this page will be updated as our policies change so that you are always able to review our policy and be aware of any information we collect, how we use it, and the purpose for collecting such data.
Information Collected By Net Shift Media Inc.
Every computer that is connected to the Internet is provided with an IP (”Internet Protocol”) address and domain name. This information is logged in an access log for each HTTP request you make to our web server and it does not reveal any personal data about you; the information gathered includes:
Your IP address and domain name
IP address and domain of the site that referred you, if any
Browser name and version number you used to access our site
Operating system platform used to access our site
Search terms used to find our site if you are referred from a search engine
Date and time of your visit
Pages/files accessed during your visit
The collection of such data has become a de facto standard by virtually every web server on the Internet today.
This data is collected for internal, Net Shift Media, use only and will not be shared, sold, rented, or provided to any third-party. Using these access logs, we are able to pinpoint and correct website technical issues, should any arise. This includes browser compatibility issues, accessibility issues, and website errors. As well, using this statistical data allows us to track the amount of traffic to our site, search terms used to find our site, and visitor patterns to measure our online marketing efforts in driving traffic to our site.
E-mail Addresses
We have no automatic way of collecting your e-mail address, and will only be able to obtain your e-mail address if you specifically provide it to us.
Because of our strict “anti-spam” policy, we will never disclose your e-mail address to a third-party without your consent. In providing us with your e-mail address, you are agreeing to communicate with us via e-mail, and are authorizing us to send relevant e-mails to your account. If at any time you do not want to receive e-mails from us, simply contact us and request that we discontinue any e-mail communication to your account.
Cookies
“Cookies” are small packets of information that are placed on your computer by our web server. These packets of information cannot be read by any other web site, and they cannot read any information contained on your hard drive. These cookies are meant to save user experience settings to enhance your visit to our site.
Most browsers will accept cookies by default, but they are easily turned off through your web browser settings. Typically you are able to disable all cookies, enable all cookies, or set your browser to notify you of every cookie that is trying to be placed on your computer. Cookies are a common feature of a majority of web sites on the Internet. Disabling cookies will not diminish the user experience on Net Shift Media’s web site. In accessing this site with cookies enabled in your browser, you are authorizing us to place a small cookie on your computer.
Contact Form
If you contact us via our contact form, we will request your name, e-mail, phone number, and applicable information pertaining to your request. Optional fields include your company name, and web address. This information is needed to respond to your message, and the optional fields give us further information to perform a more appropriate follow-up upon receiving your message. The checkbox to join our newsletter is optional, and if it is checked, you are granting us permission to send periodic e-mails to your e-mail account as part of our newsletter. If you do subscribe to our newsletter we will keep your e-mail safe as mentioned in the above section “E-mail Addresses.”
Other Information Net Shift Media May Request
We may request further information about you in the event that you contact us regarding projects, general information, or by completing a survey. The information requested is only meant for us to contact and follow up with you upon receiving your contact. We will use this information in order to process your inquiry and make an appropriate follow-up where necessary. By providing any information to Net Shift Media you are agreeing to send that information to Net Shift Media, and allowing us to receive such information. In the event that we request further information, required and optional fields will be clearly marked so that you only have to provide us with the information that you desire, and need to. Keep in mind, however, that as much information provided helps us meet your needs better.
Non-disclosure
Net Shift Media will hold all data provided to us in the strictest confidence. We will not disclose your request, or contact information to any other third-party. We have a strict “anti-spam” policy that means we will not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your e-mail address to a third-party without your consent.
Questions About This Policy?
To contact Net Shift Media about this policy, please contact:
Jarrod Goddard
#1-929 Laval Crescent
Kamloops, BC
V2C 5P4
- or -
e-mail: privacy@netshiftmedia.com
Copyright 2002-2020 Net Shift Media Inc. All Rights Reserved
Last Revision: September 28th, 2011
Net Shift Media Inc.
954F Laval Crescent
Kamloops, BC, V2C 5P5
Canada
Find us on Google+
Kamloops Website Design
Contact Us
Local: 1.250.314.0898
Toll Free: 1.855.netshift
E-mail: sales@netshiftmedia.com
Internet MarketingStrategic Web Site AuditKeyword ResearchSearch Engine Optimization (SEO)Pay-Per-Click (PPC) MarketingSocial Media MarketingE-mail MarketingWeb AnalyticsWeb Site DesignInformation ArchitectureWeb Blog DesignMobile Web Site DesignE-commerce Web Site DesignWeb Site AccessibilityWeb Site UsabilityWeb Application DevelopmentWeb Site Content Management SystemSocial Network & Community SoftwareE-commerce & Shopping Cart SoftwareIntranet/Extranet DevelopmentCustom Blog SoftwareWeb Site Hosting
Copyright © 2002-2020 Net Shift Media Inc. All Rights Reserved
SitemapPrivacy PolicyTerms of UseAccessibility Statement
